pursonalityplus.com 2012-03-27

# Pursonality Plus » Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

* * *

Our Privacy Policy :

We at PursonalityPlus.com recognizes that your privacy is important. This document

outlines the types of personal information we receive and

collect when you use PursonalityPlus.com, as well as some

of the steps that we take to safeguard your information. We hope this

will help you make an informed decision about sharing your

personal information with us.

PursonalityPlus.com endeavors to maintain the highest

standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our

operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our

customers’, consumers’ and online visitors’ privacy on our

website.

**Your Personal Information:**

PursonalityPlus.com does collect personally identifiable

information from the visitors to our website only on a

voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a

voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email

address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information

from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign

up to join our email list or request some other service or

information from us. The information collected is internally

reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify

our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in

our files. If we make material changes in the collection of

personally identifiable information we will inform you by

placing a notice on our site. Personal information received

from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and

will not be sold or provided to third parties.

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons:**

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online

experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to

your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to

enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of

a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to

a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites

pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie

enables PursonalityPlus.com to recall your specific

information on subsequent visits.

You also have the ability to accept or decline cookies by

modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to

decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the

interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor

your journey around a single website or collection of sites.

They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used

by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic.

They may be used in association with cookies to understand

how visitors interact with the pages and content on the

pages of a web site.

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and

web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web

site to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an

advertisement. No personally identifiable information you have

give us is  provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so

they cannot personally identify you with that information on

our web site.

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google,

which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the

DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based

on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You

may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google at their

site and referring to the Google as and content network

privacy policy.

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify

you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be

used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions

shouldn’t cause a problem with our site, should you so

choose.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to

children under the age of 13. We operate our site in

compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection

Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal

information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Non-Personal Information**

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is

not personally identifiable. We use this information, which

does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to

administer the site, to track users’ movements around the

site and to gather demographic information about our user

base as a whole.  The information collected is used solely

for internal review and not shared with other organizations

for commercial purposes.

**Release of Information**

If PursonalityPlus is sold, the information we have

obtained from you through your voluntary participation in

our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale

in order that the service being provided to you may

continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our

website of that change in control and practices, and we will

make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors

any opt-out requests you might make of us.

**How You Can Correct or Remove Information**

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our

commitment to protect your personal information. If you have

submitted personal information through our website and would

like that information deleted from our records or would like

to update or correct that information, please click on this

link and/or use our Contact Us page.

**Updates and Effective Date**

PursonalityPlus.com reserves the right to make changes in

this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy

practices, we will let you know on our site that our privacy

practices have changed and we will also provide a link to that new privacy

policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy

so that you will know what information we collect and how we

use it.

**Agreeing to Terms**

If you do not agree to the PursonalityPlus.com Privacy

Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use

this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy

policy.

* * *

Our Disclaimer PursonalityPlus.com Our Disclaimer

PursonalityPlus.com provides this website as a service to our viewrs.

While the information contained within the site is periodically updated, no guarantee is given that the information provided in this website is correct, complete, and/or up-to-date.

The materials contained on this website are provided for general information purposes only and do not constitute legal or other professional advice on any subject matter. (Company or website name) does not accept any responsibility for any loss which may arise from reliance on information contained on this site.

Permission is given for the downloading and temporary storage of one or more of these pages for the purpose of viewing on a personal computer. The contents of this site are protected by copyright under international conventions and, apart from the permission stated, the reproduction, permanent storage, or retransmission of the contents of this site is prohibited without the prior written consent of (company or website name).

Some links within this website may lead to other websites, including those operated and maintained by third parties. (Company or website name) includes these links solely as a convenience to you, and the presence of such a link does not imply a responsibility for the linked site or an endorsement of the linked site, its operator, or its contents (exceptions may apply).

This website and its contents are provided “AS IS” without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement.

Reproduction, distribution, republication, and/or retransmission of material contained within this website are prohibited unless the prior written permission of (company or website name) has been obtained.

* * *
